(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-07-29T01:44:31.458454",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Secret Society holoX La+ Darknesss
Secret Society holoX Takane Lui
Secret Society holoX Hakui Koyori
Secret Society holoX Kazama Iroha
Secret Society holoX Anniversary Parade
Enjoy the parade!
全世界、激震！
A worldwide shockwave!
あの超大作が
That massive blockbuster...
ついに、スクリーンへ！！
is finally coming to screens!!
タイムリミットは24時間
The time limit is 24 hours.
人類の希望は
Humanity's hope...
4人の「」に託された
has been entrusted to four...
なんだ？ここは！？
Where on earth is this!?
どうして…こんなのひどいよ！！
Why... how could this be so cruel?!
私のことはもういい！先に行け！
Don't worry about me! Go on ahead!
いろは～～～！！！お前ふざんけんなー！！
Iroha—!!! Are you kidding me?!
私たちの絆は、永遠！
Our bond is eternal!
みんなで人類を救うんだ！！
We're going to save humanity together!!
絶対に忘れないよ…
I'll never forget...
自分史上、最高傑作です
This is my greatest masterpiece ever.
holoX4周年サイコー！
holoX 4th Anniversary is the best!
犯人は……この中にいる！
The culprit... is among us!
これはお…
This is...
背後から刀で一振り…
Slain from behind with a single sword stroke...
探偵殿、どうしたでござるか？
Detective, what's the matter?
怪しい。
Suspicious.
殺人犯と一緒の場所にいられるか！部屋に戻させてもらう！
How can I stay in the same place as a murderer! I'm going back to my room!
怪しい。
Suspicious.
……ふふふふふ
Hehehehe...
怪しい。
Suspicious.
最初から最後までハラハラドキドキでしたー！
It was thrilling and heart-pounding from start to finish!
holoX4周年サイコー！
holoX 4th Anniversary is the best!
私の名前は博衣こより！どこにでもいる普通の高校生！
My name is Hakui Koyori! Just your average high school girl!
ただ一つ人と違うことは科学が好き…ってところかな？
The only thing that makes me different is that I love science... I guess?
いっけなーい！遅刻遅刻──！きゃー！
Oh no, I'm late, I'm late! Eek!
いったー！
Ouch!
見つけた。
Found you.
一緒にいると、なんか安心するでござる。
Being together somehow gives me peace of mind.
いただきまーす！あっ、最悪！うわ、これ、しれい…お姉…
Bon appétit! Ah, worst case! Woah, this command... big sis...
個性あふれる4人が紡ぐ甘ちょっぱい四角な物語──
A bittersweet quadrangle story woven by four eccentric girls—
甘ちょっぱさが絶妙でしたー！
The bittersweetness was exquisite!
holoX4周年サイコー！
holoX 4th Anniversary is the best!
あ、あなた……！holoX4周年を検索しちゃったんですか！！！
Ah, you...!! Did you search for the holoX 4th Anniversary?!
決して、検索してはイケナイ「#SSholoX4周年」
You must never search for "#SSholoX4thAnniversary"!
"holoX4周年"を検索した人間に降りかかる数々の出来事
The events that befall anyone who searches for "holoX 4th Anniversary"
ルイ姉…
Lui-nee...
いろは、大丈夫だから…
Iroha, it's alright...
いろは？
Iroha?
ぽわー！
Powa!
すごい悲鳴！
What a scream!
終始、取り乱しっぱなしでしたー！
We've been completely flustered the whole time!
せーの！
Ready, set!
holoX 4周年サイコー！
holoX 4th anniversary is the best!
迷宮ラビリンス
Maze labyrinth
召喚された正体城
The summoned true castle
秘密で解くの秘密ゲーム Mansion
A secret game solved in secret, mansion
方々のもとあの娘あの子に
From shoulder to shoulder, to that girl, that child...
ドーメー ドーゲ アジェ
Dome, doge, agenda
照らすは北欧愛
Illuminating that Nordic love
狭まる北欧はオーライ
Closing in on Nordic is alright
本能ぞに突っ込もう どうだろうこのソロターン
Let's dive into instinct, I wonder how this solo turn is
エクスに閉じ込められていくよ
Getting trapped inside Ex
核心で飾れ
Decorate with the core
不条理な迷宮脱出は
An absurd escape from the maze
終わらないトワイライト
Is an endless twilight
さあ稼ごう夜よりピュア 響き合え 笑い声へ
Come on, let's earn purer than the night, resonate into laughter
ララパッパ…
La la papa...
ひっそり本気 力こそパワー 素敵な迷宮のラビリンス
Quietly serious, might is power, a wonderful labyrinth of maze
迷宮脱出のL.A.P.L.U.S
Escaping the labyrinth, L.A.P.L.U.S
恐怖病伝説でWi-Fi
Wi-Fi with the phobia legend
ここで街で最強ルームだけど
The strongest room in town here, but
刀の回路は普通にアブマイセルフ
The sword's circuit is ordinarily 'about myself'
ワンショットでバンキリ
Ban-kill with one shot
奇怪日踊るマリオネット 落ちる部屋はダークメット
Marionettes dancing on strange days, the falling room is a dark met
ランク外はがんじがらめ ガラクタマーク
Unranked is tangled up, junk marks
エクスに取り込まれてく
Being absorbed into Ex
迷える子羊ちゃんたち お砂糖スパイス それとピンクな4周年で ハイになれるドリンクできたよ
Lost little lambs, sugar, spice, and pink 4th anniversary, made a drink that makes you high!
たっぷり飲んでくださいね
Please drink up plenty!
holoXースタジニー ノームでこばれ
holoX studio normal spill
笑い合った いやお前が飲むんかい
Laughing together—wait, you're the one drinking it?!
じゃあトドメへと行こう カワイイ！
Then let's go for the finish! Cute!
神代の街道から
From the ancient highway
定用ノレイショーケホル
Summoning the family heirloom
塗り替えられる情愛 見出ろ
Love that gets repainted, let's find our way
笑い声へ
To laughter
ララパッパ…
La la papa...
ララパタ パラ ラパタ
La lapata pa la lapata
テーテンノ 海を越えるため
To cross the sea of Eden,
ラパタ ララ ラパタ
Lapata la la lapata
ララ ラパタ
La la lapata
テーテンノ 海を越えるため
to cross the sea of Eden,
つまり本気 不屈が痛い
I mean, earnestness and resilience hurt,
テキーラ イェイ のスーパー フューチャー パーティ ラビリンス
a tequila-yay super future party labyrinth!
ラビリティ-
Lability—
ということで！
And so!
5周年ね！
It's our 5th anniversary!
早いね！
Time flies!
It really does!
おめでとう！
Congratulations!
よかった！よかった！
Wonderful! Wonderful!
おめでとう！おめでとう！
Congratulations! Congratulations!
じゃあちょっとね、これからの活動の抱負を…
Now then, let's talk about our aspirations...
早いね、展開。
That development is fast.
早いね。うん。私から？
It is. Yeah. From me?
私から？
From me?
え、聞いてないよ！
Eh, I haven't heard about this!
どうしようかな。ええ…
What should I do? Um...
みんな、ありがとう！
Everyone, thank you!
ありがとう！ありがとう！
Thank you! Thank you!
ええと、どうしようかな。
Um, what should I do?
ええ、5年目は…うん、がんばるぞ！
Um, for the 5th year... Yeah, we'll do our best!
ホロックスがんばるぞ！がんばるぞ！
holoX, let's do our best! Do our best!
おめでとう！おめでとう！
Congratulations! Congratulations!
ありがとう！ありがとう！
Thank you! Thank you!
ええ、この5年目は4人をもっと団結力をぐっと！
Um, for this 5th year, the four of us will tighten our unity even more!
ぐっと！ぐっと！そろそろ…
Tight! Tight! Soon...
日本制服ぐらいはしていきたいなと…
I'd like us to at least wear Japanese school uniforms...
日本制服！
Japanese school uniforms!
5年目はPラインとかね。世界はまだちょっと難しいけど。
For the 5th year, maybe a P-line too. The world is still a bit difficult, though.
日本制服がんばります！
We'll do our best with Japanese school uniforms!
トレるで行くぞ！クロハシ！
Let's go with Toroler! Kurohashi!
はい、みなさん、ご、ご、5周年のご！ということで5年目もね、元気に！
Hi everyone, go, go, go for the 5th anniversary, go! And so, for the 5th year too, energetically!
すこやかに、健康に、活動がんばっていきたいと思います！
healthily, wholesomely, we want to keep doing our best!
ホロックス5周年がん…5周年がんばるぞ！
holoX 5th anniversary, let's... 5th anniversary, let's do our best!
5周年までがんばろうまた！
Let's keep doing our best until the 5th anniversary!
今年も…生き残るぞ！
This year too... we will survive!
毎年生き残ること言ってるよね。
You say we'll survive every single year.
でも生き残れた今年も…そして！
But since we survived this year too... And!
5年目こそ、われわれの年にするぞ！するぞ！
For the 5th year especially, we'll make it our year! Our year!
ちょっと待って、ダサい。ダサすぎる！なんで？同じなんだけど。
Wait a minute, that's lame. Way too lame! Why? It's the exact same.
小夜梨とダサさはどうでもいいです。
Koyori's and your lameness doesn't matter.
ちょっとみんな見てくださいよ！
Hey, everyone, please look at this!
ライブステージ、すごい！めちゃくちゃかっこよくない！？
The live stage is amazing! Isn't it super cool?!
ホロックスの最初のさあ、登場からさ、うちらかっこよかったね。
holoX's very first entrance and all, we looked so cool right from the start.
かっこよかった！かっこよかった！
We looked cool! We looked cool!
でもかっこよかったけどさ、ホロックスすぐ助けられいちゃったからね。
But even though we looked cool, holoX got rescued right away.
このステージ、ただ広いだけじゃなくて、いろんな仕掛けがありますので…
This stage isn't just large, there are various gimmicks as well...
なんかね、出てきたりとか…耳入ったり…
Like appearing, or ears going in...
上がったりとかさ！変形したりとかさ！
And going up, or transforming!
合体したりとかさ！
Or merging!
流石に無理だろ！合体は！
That's obviously impossible! Merging is!
合体はできなかったですけど。
Merging wasn't possible, though.
声もそういうの大好きなんだけど、ちょっとさすかにホロックス予算が少なく…
I love that kind of stuff too, but honestly holoX's budget is a bit low...
当たり前じゃないですか！
Isn't that obvious?!
小夜梨の給料もっといいよね、稼いできてくれてもね。
Koyori's salary would be better if she brought in more earnings.
でもこのステージできたからいいじゃん！
But since we could do this stage, it's fine!
ということで5年目もホロックスのみなさん、ぜひこんな私たちですけど、よろしくお願いします！
And so, for the 5th year too, everyone in holoX, please treat us well even though we're like this!
ここでお知らせがございまーす！
We have an announcement here!
ほら、お知らせだよ！ホロライブ公式チャンネルのメンバーシップに入ると…
Look, it's an announcement! If you join the official Hololive channel membership...
なんと限定絵文字スタンプが使えるようになりますので、ぜひコメントで使って盛り上げてください！
You'll be able to use limited emoji stamps, so please use them in the comments to hype things up!
さらに、なんと今日からもう一つメンバーシップ特典があるらしいんですけども、なんと先日発表した新曲「好きでか」と「プライベートアイズ」の壁紙も貰えちゃいます！えっ！絵文字？俺たちが欲しい！
Furthermore, it seems there's another membership perk starting today, and surprisingly, we can also get wallpapers for the newly announced songs "Sukideka" and "Private Eyes"! Eh? Emojis? We want them!
え、俺たちも入らなきゃいけないの？え、俺たちも入れるの？(笑)
Eh, do we have to join too? Eh, can we join too? (laughs)
ねぇそうよ
Hey, that's right.
はい！そして、本日は何やらライブだけではなく、
Yes! And today, not just a live performance,
え、重要な情報がもりもりもりもりもりだくさんらしいので、
um, there's apparently a whole ton of important info,
もりもりもりもりもりだくさんらしいので、
a whole bunch of info,
最後までちゃんと見ていくように！私たちの…もりだくさん、じゃなくて、こつた…えー、検死です。よろしくお願いします！
so make sure to watch until the end! We're... wait, not a lot... kotsuta, um, Kenshi. Nice to meet you!
森の字を作る…
Making the kanji for "mori"...
やめとけやめとけ！
Stop that, stop that!
混ざれよ！混ざれよ！
Blend in! Blend in!
ちょっと待ってください！何なんですか？
Wait a minute! What is it?
早くしないと、みんなに見せらんないからライブ！
If we don't hurry, we can't show everyone the live!
はい、早速！最初は…
Yes, right away! First is...
こよちゃんの方から！せーの、じゃーん！
From Koyori-chan! Ready, go! Ta-da!
かわいいかわいい！何なのそれ、別々に…
So cute, so cute! What is that, separately...
かわいいか！せーの、じゃーん！
So cute! Ready, ta-da!
ちょっとちょっと！あ、かわいいね！
Wait, wait! Ah, cute!
かわいいかわいい！せーの、じゃーん！バイバレー！見ててねー！
So cute, so cute! Ready, ta-da! Bye-bye! Watch us!
見てるよ！がんばれ！走って！ほらそこ広いから走って！もうせっかちなんだから！
We're watching! Do your best! Run! Look, it's wide over there, run! You're so impatient!
あ、邪魔だから行くよ！あ、え、え、私たちも？
Ah, it's in the way, let's go! Ah, eh, eh, us too?
こっちこっち！
This way, this way!
早く！早く！行こうぜ！早く早く！
Hurry! Hurry! Let's go! Hurry, hurry!
ラブは揮発性 存在自体マジカル
Love is volatile, existence itself is magical,
調整は未完成 トキメキのケミカル
adjustment incomplete, a fluttering chemical.
(ん、なるほど) そんじゃコレならどうか！と 日進月歩なラボラトリー
(Hmm, I see) So how about this?! A lab advancing day by day.
混ぜるほどに 甘くなるなる 奇跡的に 美味しくなれ！
The more it's mixed, the sweeter it gets. Miraculously, become delicious!
フラスコにハート やべぇラテアート
A heart in the flask, awesome latte art.
効果のテスト キミが1号
Effect test, you're number one.
ドーカーンだ！ケミストリー ラブ
Boom! Chemistry love.
アイマイなキミ クロマドグラフィー
You, ambiguous chromatography.
「変」は「恋」のジェネリック
"Strange" is the generic for "love".
もっと夢中になれ なれ！
Get even more obsessed, go on!
キュンって 仕留めたいキミの胸
Thumping desire to shoot through your chest.
爆ラブ！キミと！ケミストリー！
Explosion love! With you! Chemistry!
溶けるくらい ドキドキするはず？
You should be thrilled enough to melt?
そっちのタイプの ドキドキじゃなーい！
That's not the kind of thrill I mean!
だけどまあ、ある意味 成功かなっ？
But well, in a sense, is it a success?
ラブは不溶性 勢い余って ラジカル
Love is insoluble, overly vigorous, radical.
調整は試作中 今度はどーですかっ！
Adjustment is in trial, how is this time?!
そんなトライ and 破砕を キミと重ねてく
Such trials and crushes, piling them up with you.
キュートさ 目指せ バクテリアファージ
Aim for cuteness, bacteriophage.
ラボで夢見る キミの1番
Dreaming in the lab, your number one.
中毒症状 いかがですか？
How are your addiction symptoms?
ぼくがキミの アンチドート
I am your antidote.
ドーカーンだ！ケミストリー ラブ
Boom! Chemistry love.
アイマイなキミ クロマドグラフィー
You, ambiguous chromatography.
「変」は「恋」のジェネリック
"Strange" is the generic for "love".
どんなボキも 観測して？
Observe any version of me?
さあ！ドーカーンだ！キミ＋アイ
Now! Boom! You + I.
化け尽くして 爆ぜちゃうシナジー
Transforming completely, a bursting synergy.
「キミ」こそが「アイ」のアトミック！
"You" are the atomic of "I"!
もっと夢中になろ なろっ！
Get even more obsessed, go on!
キュンって 仕留めたいキミの胸
Thumping desire to shoot through your chest.
爆ラブ！キミと 追加検証！
Explosion love! Additional verification with you!
ぎゅっ てして ぼくの胸
Hug me tight against your chest.
爆ラブ！キミと！ケミストリー！
Explosion love! With you! Chemistry!
実験は！キミと！エターナリー！
The experiment! With you! Eternally!
ドーカーンだ！ケミストリー ラブ
Boom! Chemistry love.
アイマイなキミ クロマドグラフィー
You, ambiguous chromatography.
「変」は「恋」のジェネリック
"Strange" is the generic for "love".
もっと夢中になろ なろっ！
Get even more obsessed, go on!
キュンって 仕留めたいキミの胸
Thumping desire to shoot through your chest.
爆ラブ！キミと 追加検証！
Explosion love! Additional verification with you!
ぎゅっ てして ぼくの胸
Hug me tight against your chest.
爆ラブ！キミと！ケミストリー！
Explosion love! With you! Chemistry!
実験は！キミと！エターナリー！
The experiment! With you! Eternally!
キミが好きって この感情に潰されてる
Crushed by this feeling of liking you.
足りないのは どちらの方がどうでもいいかも
What's lacking is which one matters more, maybe.
興味ないよ ねぇ責任持ってよ
I'm not interested, hey, take responsibility!
「キミが好き」ってこの感情に押し潰されてる
"I like you," I'm being crushed by this emotion,
足りない脳はどちらの方かどうでもいいっか、もう
Which of us is more brainless? Whatever, I don't care anymore.
傷付いていたって知らない様ね責任逃れ
You don't even notice I'm hurt, shifting the blame.
「私なんで好きなんだっけ？」って問い出す流れ
"Why do I even like you?" I keep asking myself.
最低なあなたへ
To you, the worst,
アタシ興味ないよ、キミなんて
I'm not interested at all in someone like you.
マジ半端ないね、舐めた真似
Seriously, you're unbelievable, acting all nonchalant.
ポップでキッチュなこの恋に
In this pop and kitschy love,
壊されちゃえばいい
I'd be fine if it destroyed me.
止めどないよキミの愛を独り占めしたい
I won't let go, I want to keep all your love to myself.
毒だろうとなんだろうが抱きしめてあげたい
Whether it's poison or whatever, I want to hold you tight.
ライセンス契約独占のフォールラブ逃がさないずっと
Fall in love under an exclusive license contract, never letting you go.
「キミが好き」ってこの感情に騙されてる
"I like you," I'm being deceived by this emotion.
大事な方は君か私か決め兼ねてる
Can't decide which of us is more important, you or me.
バカ過ぎる君へ
To you, who's just too foolish,
アタシ興味ないよ、キミなんて
I'm not interested at all in someone like you.
ほら振り回してよ好きなだけ
Look, push me around as much as you like.
ロックでVIPなこの愛は
This rock and VIP love of ours,
渡さないから
I won't let you pass.
「バカだよね」「色ボケだね」
"You're an idiot," "You're infatuated,"
「それ見たことか」とかもう
"I told you so," and all that.
他でもない貴方に呪われたまま
Still cursed by you, and no one else.
いや興味ないよ、キミなんて
No, I'm not interested at all in you.
バカなフリしてあげただけ
I just pretended to be stupid for you.
愛と愛をぶつけ合ってぐちゃぐちゃになって
Colliding love with love, turning into a messy blur.
アタシ興味ないよ、キミなんて
I'm not interested at all in you.
マジ半端ないね、舐めた真似
Seriously, you're unbelievable, acting all nonchalant.
ポップでキッチュなこの恋に壊されちゃえばいい
In this pop and kitschy love, I'd be fine if it destroyed me.
いや興味ないよ、キミなんて
Yeah, I'm not interested at all in someone like you.
バカなふりしてあげただけ
Just playing dumb and acting nice to you.
愛と愛をぶつけ合って
Making love and affection push and shove,
ぐちゃぐちゃになって
falling completely apart.
アタシ興味ないよ、キミなんて
I'm not interested at all in you.
マジ半端ないね、舐めた真似
Seriously, you're unbelievable, acting all nonchalant.
ポップでキッチュなこの恋に壊されちゃえばいい
In this pop and kitschy love, I'd be fine if it destroyed me.
壊されちゃえばいい
I'd be fine if it destroyed me.
見た目だけじゃ笑われない
Just looking at your face isn't enough,
私のこと可愛いわけと
My sweet side is just for you, you know?
まさかと思っていないよね私の本当
You couldn't possibly imagine my true self.
知ってほしい
I want you to know it.
予測誤算の範囲度
Exceeding the limits of predictability,
不足文字代も閉じない
Even the missing characters are not closed.
いつも忙しいペースでいるけど
I might look busy all the time,
心は常に青色の雲へ
My heart is always soaring in azure skies.
諦めはしない寂しがりもしない
I won't give up, I won't feel lonely either.
私負けない
I won't let you defeat me.
扱いやすいやつの伴う
Treating me like a cheap companion,
甘く見ると二度目に抜く
Getting a glance, then a second look.
それでも時には逃げ出してしまいたい
Even so, sometimes I just want to run away.
そんな衝動に汚れ吐き出す夜もある
Such impulses overflow into the dark night.
ほんの小さな小さな妥協が積み重なり重なりだって動けない
Such tiny, tiny compromises piling up,
大きな大きな可能性の枷を未来を背負い込んでしまうから
I'll exhaust every single possibility,
どんなに苦しみを抱えても苦しみだけはしない
No matter how much I struggle or suffer,
生き方なんて見つけじゃなくて
I don't need to look for how to live,
現実を離れ外との距離を縮められたとしても
I just want to close the distance to reality as I grow older.
おもむちペースでいるだけ
Just staying at my own pace,
何事もなかったかのように
Like nothing ever happened at all.
カスタマーにはしない後戻りもしない
I won't be a customer, I won't turn back,
夢も捨てない
I won't throw away my dreams.
らしいとか悲しく
That's what makes me feel like myself.
ホントノワタシ 知らないくせに
Even though you don't know the real me,
全部分かった顔してさ
you act like you understand everything...
それでも時には
Even so, at times,
温もりが恋しい
I yearn for warmth.
そんな感情に
Swept up in such emotions,
流されて果てしない夜もある
there are endless nights.
こんな甘い 甘い 言葉だけ求めてしまうような弱さなら
If this weakness makes me seek only sweet, sweet words,
いっそ苦い経験だって 私を強くしてくれるから
even bitter experiences will make me stronger.
こんな辛い 辛い 世界の果てまで 駆け抜けて生きてくんだから
So I'll run through to the end of this painful, painful world and live on!
これが これが 私のホント
This is, this is my true self.
もっと狭い 狭い 世界の中からだけで
From within a narrower, narrower world,
笑ってた自分じゃつまらないから
the me who was just smiling isn't fun anymore.
もっと広い 広い 世界の果てまで
To the edge of a broader, broader world,
駆け抜けて生きてくんだから
I'll run through and live on!
どんなに苦しくってくたくそでも楽しんでやるんだ
No matter how painful or exhausting, I'll enjoy it!
生きてるをもう見せちゃえばなくて 生き方なんだから
Show off what it means to be alive—that's my way of life!
はい ちょーもく
Yes, attention!
アレもコレもソレもたぶんタブー
This and that and that are probably taboo.
わ わかってるの？ what is 常識
Do you even understand? What is common sense?
ぷーすかぱーすか グチグチ愚痴じゃナンセンス
Complaining endlessly is utter nonsense.
わ+わかってない！
You don't understand!
（集まれっしゃい）
(Come and gather!)
後悔がベスティー 狭心症キャパシティ
Regret's my bestie, angina pectoris capacity.
ビビりじゃ負けない 比べない あげる絶句ビンタ
I won't lose to cowardice, no comparisons, here's a speech-stealing slap!
表面上だけ always 漂白しても ねぇ？
Even if you bleach just the surface, right?
痛いの痛いの 飛んでいけないくらい
Pain, pain, go away—to a degree that can't be flown off,
称賛 圧巻 毛細胞で 能な鷹は爪出しましょう
With praise, a masterpiece, and hair cells, a hawk without ability should show its claws!
あたし アナスタシスガール
I am an Anastasis Girl,
不滅量産型女 (サタン！)
an immortal mass-produced woman (Satan!)
だから なん なん なん なん なん
So what, what, what, what, what?
いち に の さん で dun, dun, dun
One, two, three, and dun, dun, dun.
アナスタシスガール
Anastasis Girl,
昨日イジメた罰 (あはん)
punishment for bullying yesterday (Ahan).
君は なん なん なん なん なん
You, what, what, what, what, what?
地獄へ だんだんだんだん だんだんだん
Down, down, down, down to hell!
革命 go ride 革命 go ride 革命 go ride
Revolution go ride, revolution go ride, revolution go ride,
アナスタシスガール
Anastasis Girl!
(お口チャック) 皆で花一匁
(Shut your mouth) Everyone, play Hana Ichi Monme.
(お口チャック) アタシだけに幸あれ
(Shut your mouth) May only I have happiness.
健やかなる時も 病める時も
In times of wellness and in times of sickness,
(前頭葉) 人間らしくあれ
(Frontal lobe) be human.
(どうも) 美の微調整が不可欠
(Thanks) Fine-tuning of beauty is indispensable.
die or die or die or die
痛いの痛いの
Pain, pain, go away—
飛んでいけないならば
if you can't fly it away,
やっちゃえ いっちゃえ 精神論で
do it, go for it, with spirit theory!
目には目を 致してやりましょう
Let's do an eye for an eye!
あたし アナスタシスガール
I am an Anastasis Girl,
プレイコードの時間
time for the play code!
だから なん なん なん なん なん
So what, what, what, what, what?
いち に の さん で dun, dun, dun
One, two, three, and dun, dun, dun.
アナスタシスガール
Anastasis Girl,
極めて遺憾です (あはん)
it is extremely regrettable (Ahan).
君は なん なん なん なん なん
You, what, what, what, what, what?
地獄へ だんだんだんだん だんだんだん
Down, down, down, down to hell!
革命 go ride 革命 go ride 革命 go ride
Revolution go ride, revolution go ride, revolution go ride,
アナスタシスガール
Anastasis Girl!
(あう あう) お願いほっといて
(Ah, ah) Please leave me alone.
とびっきりの嘘とウソが飛び散ったシャツ (shoot)
A shirt scattered with the best lies and lies (shoot).
汚れと慣れの果てが生み出したドンギバアップ
A "don't give up" born from the end of dirt and habit.
あたし アナスタシスガール
I am an Anastasis Girl,
不滅量産型女
an immortal mass-produced woman.
だから なん なん なん なん なん
So what, what, what, what, what?
いち に の さん で dun, dun, dun
One, two, three, and dun, dun, dun.
アナスタシスガール
Anastasis Girl,
昨日イジメた罰
punishment for bullying yesterday.
君は なん なん なん なん なん
You, what, what, what, what, what?
地獄へ だんだんだんだん だんだんだん
Down, down, down, down to hell!
革命 go ride 革命 go ride 革命 go ride
Revolution go ride, revolution go ride, revolution go ride,
アナスタシスガール
Anastasis Girl!
スキデカ！スキはデカく回顧録？
Sukideka! Is love a grand memoir?
ラブのリポート さめやらぬ感情
Love's report, lingering emotions
バカじゃないの 目を覚まして
Aren't you being foolish? Wake up!
全然平常心で 興味と関心だらけ 晒け出してウォンチュウ
Staying totally calm, full of interest and curiosity, exposing it all, I want you!
直感で来なくちゃてこまる
If your intuition fails you'll be in trouble
マダムな肉球 構ってあげる
Like a classy paw, I'll pay attention to you
癖になりまくる 絶妙な距離感
Becoming an addiction, this exquisite distance
ゲーム近付く
Getting closer in the game
一緒デカくデカくデカくデカく！
Together, bigger, bigger, bigger, bigger!
むちゅむちゅ もっといちゃいちゃ
Mutchu-mutchu, more clinging to each other
それがないと なのか？ ラブなのか？ またまた両方なんだわ
Without that, is it love? Or both?
なしあり絶対アンダロー
There's definitely no-or-yes under there
そしてデカくデカくデカくデカく！ でかくデカく！ いいよ全部叶うからね
And bigger, bigger, bigger, bigger! Even bigger! Alright, all your wishes will come true
結局おもろいナイト！ 中の占い師は
Ultimately, an interesting night! The fortuneteller inside
大体一緒にやっていきましょう
Let's mostly keep doing this together
あんなこんな好きはデカく過ぎデカく縛っ放し！恋愛よろしくな！
This and that love is too big, boundlessly huge! Treat my love well!
スキデカ！スキデカ！スキデカ！スキデカ！スキデカ！スキデカ！スキデカ！
Sukideka! Sukideka! Sukideka! Sukideka!
たくさんの感情 みんなに伝えて
Conveying all these emotions to everyone
俺だけに魅せてくれたっていいだろ！いいだろ！
It's fine if you show it only to me! Right? Right?
一人特別さ、微塵もできません
Treating someone specially alone, I can't do even a bit
それでもいいかな
Is that still alright?
もっと知りたいことだらけ ほどほどにして
Full of things I want to know more about, keep it moderate
でも知らない方が幸せか おのじかにしてよね
But is it happier not knowing? Make it personal, won't you
絶妙な距離感 ゲームバランス 取り合う 一緒 数かず吸われず
Exquisite distance, game balance, interacting together, counting and absorbing
和つらいから 調度よくアンバイで お互いもっとわかり合えたら
It's hard, so with just the right balance, if we could understand each other better
特別になれる そうだ いつも通じ合える
We can become special, that's right, we can always connect
この先は想像できないけど 結構イカジカも ギリギリでもいいか そのまま進みます
I can't imagine what lies ahead, but even if it's cutting it close, let's just keep going
踏みつけていくよ 結局思い悩いナイト！おもろいナイト！
Stomping forward, after all, worrying all night! An interesting night!
中の占い師は
The fortuneteller inside
さあここで今後我々について話し合っていきたい！もっと見らないでしょ？いいからほら！手をつなごう Let's go!
Now let's discuss our future here! Don't you want to see more? Come on! Let's hold hands, Let's go!
一緒すれ違いが二人
Two people passing each other by chance
一緒デカくデカくデカくデカく！
Together, bigger, bigger, bigger, bigger!
なんでも頂戴サイダーな好き作りましょう
Let's make whatever love you want like cider
それがないくないの？ラブなのか？
Isn't that lacking? Is it love?
またまた両方なんだわ
Or maybe both after all?
なしあり絶対アンダロー
No or yes, it's definitely under there
そしてデカくデカくデカくデカく！ デカくデカく！いいよ全部叶うからね
And bigger, bigger, bigger, bigger! Even bigger! Alright, all your wishes will come true
結局おもろいナイト！おもろいナイト！中の占い師は なんかの占いはないわ大一緒にやっていきましょう
Ultimately, an interesting night! The fortuneteller inside has no fortune, let's do it together
一緒数かず離れず 諦めずちょうどよくアンバイで
Together, counting without separating, without giving up, with just the right balance
お前ともっとくだらないことでも迷っていたい 感動し続けあいたい
I want to keep hesitating with you even over silly things, I want to keep being moved together
この先も変わらない関係性を ちょっと行き過ぎて またちょっと切っちゃった 一旦進みます
Even going forward, an unchanging relationship... went a bit too far and cut it again, let's keep going for now
冷ます戻ります 好きはデカく！好きはデカく！
Cooling down, coming back, love is big! Love is big!
束縛ホールド 恋愛よろしくな！不思議な関係お見逃しなく
Binding hold, treat my love well! Don't miss this mysterious relationship
スキデカ！スキデカ！好きデカ！スキデカ！好きデカ！スキデカ！
Sukideka! Sukideka! Sukideka! Sukideka!
超異常現象 tenderness 行くぜ東奔西走 timeless
Super abnormal phenomenon tenderness, here we go, running east and west timeless
捨てろ劣等感 ほら最強じゃん
Discard your inferiority complex, see, we're the strongest!
今焼き付けろ 超異常現象 tenderness 行くぜ東奔西走 timeless
Now burn it into your eyes, super abnormal phenomenon tenderness, running east and west timeless
我等名探偵… いや迷探偵！さあ ba ba ba ba bang!!!
We are master detectives... No, botched detectives! Now, ba ba ba ba bang!!!
満月の夜潜り込んで ビルの隙間でため息 wow
Sneaking into the full moon night, sighing in the gap of the buildings
星のループで探し出して 深い闇へ誘い出ざなうの
Searching with the loop of stars, inviting you into the deep darkness
逮捕連関秘密のshowtime 有言実行世界を制圧
Arrest correlation, secret showtime, putting words into action, conquering the world
オレンジに染まっていくホークアイ c'mon now
Hawkeye dyeing in orange, c'on now
君のために mela mela 愛を燃焼させ me la mela
Burning mela mela for you, letting love burn me la mela
守り抜くと誓ったあの日から 未来のために mela mela
From that day we swore to protect it, mela mela for the future
この音に乗っけちゃえば 退屈なんて無縁でしょサヨナラ
If we ride on this sound, boredom is totally unrelated, goodbye
超異常現象 tenderness 行くぜ東奔西走 timeless
Super abnormal phenomenon tenderness, here we go, running east and west timeless
捨てろ劣等感 ほら最強じゃん
Discard your inferiority complex, see, we're the strongest!
今焼き付けろ 超異常現象 tenderness 行くぜ東奔西走 timeless
Now burn it into your eyes, super abnormal phenomenon tenderness, running east and west timeless
我等名探偵… いや迷探偵！さあ ba ba ba ba bang!!!
We are master detectives... No, botched detectives! Now, ba ba ba ba bang!!!
街灯が照らす欲望の影を 忍足で欺いて wow
Deceiving the shadow of desire illuminated by streetlights on stealthy feet, wow
震える手を握りしめよう 大丈夫心配ないわ
Let's clasp our trembling hands, it's alright, don't worry
変化カムフラージュ迷彩 chameleon 宙に乱射 candy chocolate
Camouflage camouflage camo chameleon, spraying candy chocolate into the air
一刀両断不安を切り裂いて 夢のために mela mela
Severing anxiety with one stroke, mela mela for our dreams
闇を燃焼させ me la mela どんな時もこの声を届けたい
Burning the darkness me la mela, wanting to deliver this voice at any time
崖っ縁で me la mela 諦めるには早いわ
On the verge me la mela, it's too early to give up
どんでも返し奇跡のおまじない また mistake 喰らう 総スキャン 綺麗 な 天然記念物
Miracle spell of turnaround, taking another mistake, total scan, a beautiful natural monument
それじゃ意味がないわ
That would mean nothing at all.
変化カウントダウンさせて ミリオン
Countdown to change, million.
銃撃ラッシュ 恋のチョコレート
Gunfire rush, chocolate of love.
エスプレッソ 濃いめサイズで
With a rich espresso size.
夢のために メラメラ 闇を燃やせ メラメラ
Burn fiercely for dreams, burn the darkness away.
どんなときもこの声を届けたい
No matter what, I want to deliver this voice.
崖っぷちで メラメラ 諦められないわ
Hanging on a cliff, burning fiercely, I won't give up.
どん底発 奇跡のおまじない
A miracle spell departing from rock bottom.
まさにセクラバ 三星・レアな天然記念
Truly secret lovers, three stars, rare natural monument.
その視線は意外と正常 立ておまじない
That gaze is unexpectedly normal, stand up and cast a spell.
そこに至って迷子になっちゃってもぷんぷんです
Even if we get lost on the way there, we're pouting.
うぞうむぞうで群れ巻いて
Swarming together like a mob of insects.
天候晴れてから エスケープ
Escape once the weather clears up.
君のためにメラメラ 愛を燃やせメラメラ
Burn fiercely for you, burn love fiercely.
守り抜くの誓った あの日から
From the day I swore to protect you.
明日のためにメラメラ この音に乗っけてば
Burn fiercely for tomorrow, riding on this sound.
退屈なんて無縁でしょ さよなら
Boredom is out of the question, goodbye.
超常現象 Phenomenon エピックでトホホ戦線さプライマレスト
Supernatural Phenomenon, epic and pitiful frontline prime rest.
ネトカノ？ それとも最強感？ 今焼き付けろ
Net girlfriend? Or the ultimate feeling? Burn it into your eyes now.
超常現象 Phenomenon エピックでトホホ戦線さプライマレスト
Supernatural Phenomenon, epic and pitiful frontline prime rest.
生まれのメンタリティ 今目覚めた 3, 2, 1, Ba-Ba-Ba-Ba-Bang!
The mentality of birth has awakened now, 3, 2, 1, Ba-Ba-Ba-Ba-Bang!
ねぇねぇねぇねぇ るいさ めっちゃ語ったね
Hey, hey, hey, hey, Lui-sa, you talked so much!
めっちゃ楽しかったね
It was super fun!
あれ めっちゃいいよね
That's super good, right?
まだ終わってないからね まだ終わってないよ
We're not done yet, we're not done yet!
これからのも最高だよね
The stuff coming up is the best too!
気づいちゃいました？
Did you notice?
足元足元足元足元足元
Look at our feet!
変じゃなーい めっちゃかっこいいじゃん
Isn't it cool? No, it's super cool!
こよが作りました！
Koyori made it!
これがござるの給料の8割 八百八町もきゅうりも変わんないからね
This is 80% of Gosaru's salary!
とゆーことで、これは
And so, this is...
告知用カードをもう見ていただいた
We've already shown you the announcement card!
とゆーことでこのカードでね、グッズ紹介でございますね
So with this card, we'll be introducing the goods!
はーい、それでは私からね 行きますよ
Alright, then I'll go first!
ホロックス活動4周年記念グッズ
holoX 4th Anniversary Goods...
Secret Society holoX Anniversary Parade 今日ノ18時より販売開始されて... されます！
Secret Society holoX Anniversary Parade is available for purchase starting at 18:00 today!
さぁ、それではそれぞれ見ていきましょう
Now, let's look at each of them one by one!
まずはプレミアムアクリル色紙だーん！ イエーイ！
First, the premium acrylic colored paper! Yay!
なんと複製サインとロゴが箔押しになっててめっちゃいい感じ！ かっこいい！
It has replica foil-stamped signatures and logos, looks so good! So cool!
そしてお次がこちら！ ホロカスリーブ！ このカードがまさにそれなんですけど
And next is this! Holoka sleeves! This card is literally it.
こちらなんと60枚入り！ わー！ やったねー！
And this comes with 60 pieces! Wow, yay!
そしてアクリルスタンド！ おー！ めっちゃかっこいい！
And the acrylic stand! Oh, so cool!
キービジュアルのデザインと表情違いになってるので、ぜひアクリル色紙と比べてみてくださいねー
The expressions are different from the key visual, so please compare them!
かっこいいー！ ふうちゃんもいれば、いろはもね、かわいいねー
So cool! Fu-chan and Iroha are also cute!
そしてこちら！ 記念メダルも発売しております！ なんとケースと巾着がついてくる記念メダルでございます
And this! We're also releasing anniversary medals with a case and pouch!
こちらね、機種ごとにデザインが異なっておりますので、なんと今回はホロックスだけのデザインになっております
The design differs for each model, exclusively for holoX!
ぜひぜひゲットしてね よーくチェックしてみてください
Be sure to get it and check it out closely!
はい、ということで次は何のカードかな？ タイミーコラボレアバイト募集！
Alright, next card is the Timee collaboration rare part-time job!
先日のタイミーで募集したレアバイトなんですけど、現地の様子があるということで、見に行ってみましょう！
Let's check out the footage from the rare part-time job recruited via Timee!
えー！？ すごい！
Ehh?! Amazing!
え、待って、待って、ほんとにholoXしてる！ ありがとうございます！
Wait, wait, they're really doing holoX! Thank you!
え、待って、待って、めっちゃ見られてる！
Wait, wait, they're being stared at so much!
holoXer! holoXer!
最後は全員いくぞ！
holoX! holoX!!
なんと数千人に1人の確率です！
タワー！タワー！
なんとなんと！
新しいサービス！
スピードは最速です！お楽しみに！
明日からコンビニでプリントアウトできるんだ！
ファミリーマート、ローソン、ミニストップになります！
そして今からネットで事前購入ができるらしいです！マジ？
詳しくは左下のリンクから確認してみてください！
さらにですね、今回はお写真にですね、ブロマイドにメッセージをつけることができるみたいなんですけれども！
というわけでこれでおねがいします！
こちらのほうどうぞ！こちらのほうどうぞ！
え！？マジで！？
What?! Seriously?!
ヤバッ！ヤバすぎ！
No way! Way too crazy!
え！？マジヤバ！
What?! Seriously crazy!
え、めっっちゃ好きじゃんね！
You love it so much, don't you?!
え、ヤバすぎる！
Seriously, way too crazy!
え、どういうこと！？
Wait, what does this mean?!
いや、でしょ
Right?
どっか行った？
Did they go somewhere?
え、でしょ！でしょ！でしょ！
Right? Right! Right!
え、ということで、ありがとうございます！
And with that, thank you very much!
はい、ありがとうございます！
Yes, thank you very much!
なんと！マジで！？怒られない我が輩？
What?! Seriously?! Will I not get scolded?
怒られない、来い来い。
You won't, come on, come on.
怒られるって、台本を用意してないからね、これ。
You'll get scolded because we haven't prepared a script, you see.
早く出しなさいよ！
Hurry up and put it out!
なんと、〈物語〉シリーズとのコラボが決定じゃ、どういうこと！？
What, a collaboration with the Monogatari Series has been decided?! What does that mean?!
どういうこと！？って、みんなも言ってる！
"What does that mean?!" Everyone is saying that too!
詳細会は随時発表されるようなので、
Details will be announced from time to time,
え、我々も知っていない。
Uh, even we don't know yet.
そうなんです！詳細の時期も大文字なんですか！？
That's right! Even the timing of the details is in large text?!
そうなんです！
That's right!
そうなんですか！？いやちょっと、なんか、
Is that so?! Well, sort of,
うちも、ちょっと焦ってるんですけど、
We're also a little panicked, but...
え、いいんですか！？いいんですかっ！ていう感じなんですけれども、
Is that okay?! Is it really okay?! That sort of feeling,
なんかちょっとね、あの最後に一つあるみたいなので、そちらをいきましょう！
It seems there's one last thing, so let's go to that!
え、もう一個見ないといけない！もう一個見ないといけないんで。
Wait, we have to look at another one! We have to look at another one.
一旦動揺、一旦動揺、動揺を落ち着けてみんな。落ち着いて、落ち着いて。
Calm down for a second, calm down, calm your panic everyone. Calm down, calm down.
その動揺してる間に、皆さんこの6つ目が何か、コメントで教えてみてください！何かな？
While you're panicking like that, everyone try telling us in the comments what this 6th one is! What could it be?
よにかな？よにかいな？
Could it be Yoni? Could it be Yonikai?
予想して、コメント見に行こ！よにかいな？なんかあるか。
Let's guess, let's check the comments! Yonikai? Is there something?
死のぶ？死のぶ？怒られないかな？え、なんだろ。何てこと、何てこと、どういうことなんだろ。
Shinobu? Shinobu? Won't we get scolded? Uh, I wonder what it is. What on earth, what on earth, what does it mean?
最後の1つは皆さんなんだと思いますか？なんだと思う？なんだと思う？
What do you all think the last one is? What do you think? What do you think?
なんとですね、まあちょっとヒントを言うと、
Well, to give a hint,
まあ、今年2局作りましたよね？
well, we made two songs this year, right?
あー！作ったね！
Ah! We did!
全部でholoXって何曲ありますか？何曲？何曲？
In total, how many songs does holoX have? How many? How many?
お、何曲だ！
Oh, how many songs?!
そして、え、あのたくさん！たくさんだ！覚えてないのか？
And, uh, a whole lot! A lot! You don't remember?
holoXが出してきた企画を除きますと、全部で7曲あります！
Excluding the projects holoX has put out, in total there are 7 songs!
え、てことは！こしや！？え？てかみんな分かってるから、みんなコメント欄分かってきてるんじゃない！？
Wait, does that mean?! Kosiya?! Eh? Wait, everyone already knows, aren't they figuring it out in the comment section?!
どうだ！？いや、あ、あ、あ、あたってる人いる！あたってる人いる！
How is it?! No, ah, ah, ah, some people are getting it right! Some people are getting it right!
ということで、気づいてる人もいるみたいなので、やっぱりあちらでございます！6枚目オープン！バーン！
So, it seems some people have noticed, so as expected, it's that one! 6th item open! Bam!
じゃん！なんと！ファーストアルバムが出ます！
Ta-da! What, a 1st album is coming out!
イェーイ！やったー！やったー！嬉しい！嬉しい！
Yay! Hooray! Hooray! I'm so happy! I'm so happy!
ということで、ファーストアルバム、ファーストオーダ…じゃない、ファーストアルバムシークレットオーダー！
And with that, the 1st album, 1st orde... no, the 1st album Secret Order!
ああ、そうだそうだ、みんな言ってるよ！そうだそうだ、あ、そうなんだよ！
Ah, right, right, everyone's saying it! That's right, that's right, oh, that's right!
こちらのシークレットオーダー、holoXでの4年間をぎゅっと詰め込んだアルバムとなっております！
This Secret Order is an album packed tightly with our 4 years in holoX!
はい、我々のデビュー曲「常夜リペイント」はオリジナルバージョンに加えて、本作のために新たにリアレンジされたバージョンも収録されています！
Yes, our debut song "Jōya Repaint" includes not only the original version, but also a newly rearranged version specifically for this work!
そしてさらに、なんかまだ未発表の楽曲も、
And furthermore, it seems some unannounced songs too—
え！？ってことは、なんかってこと？8とか9とか10とか11とか？
Eh?! Does that mean like 8, 9, 10, or 11?
増えすぎると、増えすぎる、増えすぎる。
If it increases too much, it gets too much, too much.
ということでですね、通常版になるんですけれど、あ、ちょっと、あの、上が見えないですね。
So, it's going to be the regular edition, but ah, wait, the top isn't showing.
ああ、早い早い早い、流れがね。
Ah, it's fast, fast, the flow is fast.
すみません、通常版には初回限定特典があります。
Sorry, the regular edition has a first-press limited bonus.
え、こちらでございますね。各メンバーのソロバージョン、そしてジャケット4種類のうちらんダムで1枚付きます。
Yes, here it is. A solo version of each member, and one of 4 types of jackets chosen at random will be included.
ほお、そしてこちらですね。4枚並べると、どうやら1枚絵になるとのことですよ！
Ooh, and this here. If you line up 4 of them, apparently they form a single illustration!
え、すごい、繋がっていそうな顔してる。ツッちゃん角が刀の上に。あ、本当だ。
Oh amazing, they have faces that look like they connect. Tsub-chan's horns are right above the sword. Ah, true.
そして完全生産限定版封入特典は！
And the complete production limited edition bundled bonus is!
うん、かっこよさ満点の今回のアルバムには、holoXらしい秘密の仕掛けが！秘密の仕掛け？え？我々も分かってないぞ。
Mhm, this album packed with coolness has a secret holoX-style gimmick! A secret gimmick? Eh? Even we don't know.
隠されているとか。なんだって！？はい、ちょっと私たちも分からないのですが、
It's hidden or something. What?! Yes, we don't really know either,
この後22時から販売開始です！
but sales start right after this at 22:00!
22時から、ぜひぜひご予約をお願いいたします！お願いします！
From 22:00, please make your reservations! Please!
ということで、めっっちゃ告知もりだくさんだったんですが、告知カードちゃんたちはこれで役目終わりということで、
So, there were tons of announcements, but since the announcement cards' role is done with this,
消すのどうやるの？消すのどうやるの？
how do we erase them? How do we erase them?
よいしょ！よいしょ、待って待って、ここに怒りかけすぎだろ！このギミックヤバいぞ！消すだけ消すだけ、消すだけね。
Heave-ho! Heave-ho, wait wait, you put way too much anger here! This gimmick is dangerous! Just erase, just erase, just erase.
ということで、ライブもラストスパートでございます。
With that, the live is also in its final spurt.
この後ですね、何やらちょっと、お知らせ？サプライズ？があるらしいですよ！
After this, apparently there's some kind of notice? Surprise?
はい、最後までチャンネルはそのままでおねがいいたします！
Yes, please keep the channel as is until the very end!
みんな、最後まで楽しんでいこう！いくぞー！いくぞ！
Everyone, let's enjoy it to the very end! Let's go! Let's go!
おい！おい！おい！
Oi! Oi! Oi!
そこに跪け！
Bow down before us!
吐いて捨てるような現実を
Cast aside this worthless reality!
一刀両断 叩き斬れ
Slash it to pieces in one stroke!
終わりなき輪廻に迷いし仔らよ
Lost souls wandering in endless reincarnation,
漆黒の翼で誘おう
We shall lure you with jet-black wings.
我ら エデンの星を統べるもの
We are the rulers of Eden's star,
秘密結社…
Secret society...
holoX！
holoX!
でござる！
That's right!
Who a-oh! Who a-oh-oh! Oh-oh-oh!
How low?
どうしようもないこの世界
How hopeless this world is,
どうしてほしい？
What do you want?
Black out
終末告げる鐘が鳴る
The bell announcing the end rings out.
ラッパッパッパッパッパラッパーで踊ろうぜ
Ra-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-ra-pa, let's dance!
Tripしようぜ
Let's take a trip!
陰キャも陽キャも sing a song
Introverts and extroverts alike, sing a song!
気持ちいいことだけがすべて
Only feeling good is everything,
落ちていく闇の底へ
Falling down to the depths of darkness.
甘い甘いメロディ
A sweet, sweet melody,
ほらどうぜどうぜ手の鳴る方へ
Look, towards where hands clap,
もう逃げられない
You can't escape anymore.
ほら
Look,
闇に染まれば
If you're dyed in darkness,
世界を塗り替えてろ
Repaint the world!
望めばくれてやろうすべて
We'll give you whatever you wish for,
常識破り捨てろ
Throw away common sense!
クルクル狂い倒れ火をつけろ
Spin around wildly and set it on fire!
すべてを食らい尽くせ
Devour everything!
秘密を
Our secrets...
教えてやろう
We will teach you!
Who a-oh! Who a-oh-oh! Oh-oh-oh!
悪のカリスマ導くぞ民草
The charismatic villain guides the masses,
正義とか知らないし地ならしして誘う
Inviting them by paving over things called justice,
マジメに不マジメ弊社の快楽劇
A delightful drama of our serious yet unserious company,
望み求め願い叶え世界征服
Seeking desires and granting wishes, world domination!
ラッパッパッて歌おうぜ
Ra-pa-pa-pa, let's sing!
Swingしようぜ
Let's swing!
退屈な世界へ bye bye bye
To a boring world, bye bye bye!
覚めることのない夢をみせるほら
We'll show you a dream you'll never wake from, look!
お眠りなさい
Go to sleep.
もっともっと奥へ
Deeper and deeper,
ほらどうぜどうぜ生きたいんでしょ？
Come on, you want to live, right?
もうやめられない
You can't stop anymore,
ほら
Look!
悪に染まれば
If you're stained in evil,
世界を塗り替えてろ
Repaint the world!
望むもの与えようすべて
We'll give you whatever you desire,
ルールを書き換えろ
Rewrite the rules!
クルクル回し尽くせ焼き尽くす
Spin everything around and burn it all down,
すべての紛い物へ
To all fakes and imitations!
すべてを食らい尽くせ
Devour everything!
秘密を
Our secrets...
教えてやろう
We will teach you!
Who a-oh! Who a-oh-oh! Oh-oh-oh!
時は4周年！
The time is our 4th anniversary!
狂気の宴の始まりだ！
The banquet of madness begins!
貴様ら、準備はいいか！！
You scumbags, are you ready?!
おー！！ぴ！
Ooh---!!!
刮目せよ！！
Witness this!!
クロエ！！クロエ！！
Chloe!! Chloe!!
手上げろ！手上げろ！！
Put your hands up! Put your hands up!!
いろは！！いろは！！
Iroha!! Iroha!!
叫べでござる！
Shout out!
こより！！こより！！
Koyori!! Koyori!!
踊っﾁｬｴ！踊っﾁｬｴ！！
Dance away! Dance away!!
世界をテニするholoX！
holoX taking the world!
世界を変えてくholoX！
holoX changing the world!
ルイ姉！！ルイ姉！！
Lui-nee!! Lui-nee!!
もっともっと！！
More, more!!
ラプラス！！ラプラス！！
Laplus!! Laplus!!
最後は全員いくぞ！
Everyone, let's go for the finale!
holoX！holoX！！
holoX! holoX!!
世界をテニするholoX！
holoX taking the world!
世界を変えてくholoX！
holoX changing the world!
世界をこの手にholoX！
holoX holding the world in our hands!
心を解き放て
Set your heart free,
ほらどうぜどうぜ身を任せて
Come on, surrender yourself,
もう逃げられない
You can't escape anymore.
ほら
Look,
闇に染まれば
If you're dyed in darkness,
世界を塗り替えてろ
Repaint the world!
望めばくれてやろうすべて
We'll give you whatever you wish for,
常識破り捨てろ
Throw away common sense!
クルクル狂い倒れ火をつけろ
Spin around wildly and set it on fire!
すべてを食らい尽くせ
Devour everything!
秘密を
Our secrets...
教えてやろう
We will teach you!
Who a-oh! Who a-oh-oh! Oh-oh-oh!
レッツゴー
Let's go!
機は熟した
The time is ripe.
暁闇より現れし英霊たちよ、準備はいいか!!
Spirits of the twilight, are you ready?!
おーーー！！！
Ooh!!!
Are you ready?
ラッパッパー LaPaLaPa ラッパッパー
La-pa-pa-pa, La-Pa-La-Pa, La-pa-pa-pa,
夜が深まる ほらダークネス
As night deepens, behold, darkness.
能ある鷹はPONで隠す
A wise hawk hides behind its "PON."
脳に従え Egoistic
Obey your mind, egoistic.
のっとにニン！ サムライGirl
Not to mention, samurai girl!
闇金じゃないけど フルベッドでしょ
Not loan sharks, but a full bet, right?
征服すればOK 切り裂く赤字
Conquer and it's fine, slashing red ink.
悪の手のひら 踊りたくなる ほら君も気付けば
Dancing on the palm of evil, before you know it,
ノリノリです
you're totally into it.
どうしようもない どうしようもない
Helpless, helpless,
堕ちてく運命
a falling destiny.
ならしょうがない
Can't be helped,
もう全部 塗り替えよ
repaint everything!
エクスとエクスとエクスとエクスが 交差する真ん中で
In the exact center where X's intersect,
ネクストネクストネクストネクスト 世界はもう始まってる
Next, next, next, next, the world has already begun!
(ウォッオッオ オーオーオー)
(Woah-oh-oh, ooh-ooh-ooh)
飛び出せ 闇が呼ぶ方へ
Jump out, toward where the darkness calls.
(ウォッオッオ オーオーオー)
(Woah-oh-oh, ooh-ooh-ooh)
暗黒のエクスデス
Dark Exdes.
混沌としたこの世界を我らholoX色に塗り替えるのだ！者共、かかれ！
We shall repaint this chaotic world in our holoX colors! Minions, attack!
Yes My Dark!!!
完璧漆黒∞〈アブソリュート・ダークネス・インフィニティ〉
Absolute Darkness Infinity.
エデンの星は我が手中に！
The star of Eden is in my hands!
魔眼ホーゥアイ！
Demon Eye Hawkeye!
お前もholoXerの一員となるのだ！
You too shall become a member of holoXer!
可愛いにゃむマーム♡
So cute, Nyamu Marm♡
これで君も今日よりメイトメロ！
With this, you're a mate-melo from today on too!
一刀両断 叩き切れ！
Slay cleanly with a single stroke!
どうしようもない どうしようもない
Helpless, helpless,
堕ちてく運命
a falling destiny.
ならしょうがない
Can't be helped,
もう全部 塗り替えよ
repaint everything!
かつもくせよ
Watch closely!
エクスとエクスとエクスとエクスが 交差する真ん中で
In the exact center where X's intersect,
ネクストネクストネクストネクスト 世界はもう始まってる
Next, next, next, next, the world has already begun!
(ウォッオッオ オーオーオー)
(Woah-oh-oh, ooh-ooh-ooh)
コッピナ コッピナ つまりサイコーに
Copy me, copy me, meaning, in the highest way,
(ウォッオッオ オーオーオー)
(Woah-oh-oh, ooh-ooh-ooh)
笑うのは holoXです
the ones laughing are holoX.
ラッパッパー LaPaLaPa ラッパッパー
La-pa-pa-pa, La-Pa-La-Pa, La-pa-pa-pa,
世界ヲ手ニスル 準備ハイイカ
Are you ready to take the world?
狂気ノ宴ノハジマリダ
The banquet of madness begins!
#SSholoX世界リペイント計画
#SSholoX World Repaint Project
みんなも驚いてくれてる！いかがでしたか？
Everyone's so surprised! How was it?
やばいね、早いよ... まだ早いからね！
It's crazy, so fast... It's still early!
ということで、なんと我々の現地ライブが決まりました！
And with that, our in-person live concert has been decided!
イヤー！やったー！わあ、とうとう！ありがとう！
Yay! Hooray! Wow, finally! Thank you!
ということで、みんなそれぞれね、ライブに向けて...
So everyone, toward the live concert...
意気込みを、お願いしたいと思います！
We'd like to ask for your enthusiasm!
うん。
Hmm.
まずは、じゃ私から。
First up, me!
はい！
Yes!
はあー……
Haah...
決まったな！
Okay, it's decided!
はーい！
Yes!
ねえ良かったら？
Right?
決まったな！
It's decided!
決まったね。
It's decided.
いや、めちゃくちゃね、あの、
Yeah, like, seriously...
デビューの時から
ever since our debut...
うん。
Yeah.
ライブやりたいねって、
we kept saying we wanted to do a live show,
って
right?
言ってて、デビュー前から
Even before our debut,
うん。
yeah.
それが
And now,
もうありがたいことにね。
it's wonderfully come true.
そうだよね！
That's right!
みんなの応援のおかげで、
And thanks to everyone's support,
ホロックスさんたちの応援のおかげで、
thanks to the support of the holoX fans,
叶いました！やったー！
we made it happen! Yay!
やったー！やったー！
Yay! We did it!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
ありがとうございます。
Thank you very much.
えー、もう
So, uh...
このホロックスの、みんなで
we want to hype everyone up
当日は盛り上げたいと思いますので、
on that day, so
ぜひみんな遊びに来てください！
please, everyone, come play!
かっこいいホロックスを観に来てね！
Come see the cool holoX!
観に来てね！
Come see us!
というわけで、
With that said,
続いては、じゃあこよ！
up next is... Koyori!
はい！
Yes!
えー、ま、今言ってた通りみんなライブやりたいねって話はしてたし、
So, like I was saying earlier, we talked about how everyone wanted to do a live show,
やっぱこよは、
and you know,
一番忘れられない風景が、
the most unforgettable scenery for me
初めてのフェスで、ホロックスでやった時の、
was when we did our very first festival as holoX,
あの、嬢ヶ島ペイントで会場がもう一体ってなってくれたのを浴びた時、
and when I bathed in that amazing unity paint where the venue just became one—
あれをもうずっと忘れられないんで、
I just can't ever forget that.
やっぱり、その、今度はね、
So this time,
ホロックスさんたちだけの、フェスを、俺たちの会場で、
being able to do a live show with just the holoX members,
やれるわけじゃないですか。めちゃんこ嬉しいです。
you know? I couldn't be happier!
そして、できて、本当に、この、
And I'm so grateful
やらせてくれることにさせてくれた、大人のみなさんにも、
to all the adults who made it possible for us to do this.
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
Thank you!
この4人のできる力を全て出して、そして歌とダンスもね、
We're going to put every ounce of our four-person strength into this,
より一層力を込めて、
putting even more heart into it,
お届けしますので、絶対現地、そして現地来れない人は映像でも絶対観に来てください！よろしくお願いします！
so we'll definitely give it our all!
お願いします！
Thank you!
ナイス！
Nice!
はい。
Hi.
鷹ルイ。
Lui-nee.
はい。
Hi.
みんなー！
Everyone!
生でござるたちの声が聴ける機械！
The machine where you can hear us live and in person!
ホロックスのこのハーモニーが聴ける機械！ハーモニー、ハーモニー、ハーモニー、ハーモニー！
The machine where you can hear holoX's harmony!
聴けないけどね、何よりもえ、俺たちの、
Well, I guess you could say it's...
共鳴、共鳴の限界が、ハーモニー！来たか！
the resonance of all of us!
北川！
Kitagawa!
はい！
Yes!
いやもう本当にね、ホロックス、やっぱ本当にみんな言ってるけど、
Yeah, really, holox, like everyone keeps saying,
デビュー前からね、現地ライブをこのメンバーでやりたいってずっと言っていたので、それがやっとかなってね、でかい声で出してみんなで盛り上がれるのを、
we've been saying ever since before our debut that we wanted to do a real live show together as these members,
今か今かとね、楽しみにしております！
so we're looking forward to it right now!
我々もね、4人ともしっかり当日まで、レッスンや、もうね、練習も含め、パフォーマンスも全部色々みんなに楽しんでもらえることいっぱい考えて、
All four of us are working hard right up until the big day—
挑みますので、うん。
stepping up our game!
見ている皆さんもぜひ全力で楽しみにしてしてそして当日は楽しんでください！頑張ります！盛り上げる準備できてます！がんばれー！
So everyone watching, please look forward to it with all your might, and have an amazing time on the day of the event! Let's do our best! We're ready to pump you up!
できるぞ！やれるぞ！
We can do it!
よし！
Alright!
じゃあ最後、さす、さす決めてくれ！
Now, finally...
お願いしますよ。
Please.
ちょっと、みんな、ついに
Well, everyone...
ホロックスが！ぼるたちが！ライブー！
holoX is having a live show!
やったー！
Yay!
もうみんなさ、もうすごい、ライブやりたい、音楽大好きみたいなさ、
You know, everyone,
ずっと聴いてたからさ、
we've been listening to it forever, right?
俺は嬉しいよ。
So I'm so happy!
いや、でも、当日だよ、当日だ。
Yeah, it's the real deal!
あの、やっぱりライブがね、一番楽しいから、みんなさ、やってる。
Because live shows are the most fun, right?
やっぱホロックスの活動って、なんかライブって感じじゃん。
And you know, holoX activities...
だからそれがさ、俺たちだけで、しかもホロックスがバーって咲いてるとこでできるのが、
that's why it makes me so happy
嬉しいよな。
that we can do this together.
めちゃくちゃ熱い！熱い！熱い！
It's so hot! It's so hot!
いや、本当、うちら本当に色々あったけど、
We've had a lot happen,
これからも本当に4人いれば大丈夫だから、がんばろう！
but as long as the four of us are here, it'll be fine, so let's do our best!
がんばろう！がんばろう！
Let's do our best!
一致団結して！
Let's unite as one!
ライブ、がんばるぞ！がんばるぞ！がんばるぞ！
Let's do our best! Let's go!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you!
速報です！
That was the breaking news:
トレード1という事で、
our very first live show!
ありがとうございます！ありがとうございます！
Thank you everyone!
ここから4月29日までもうね、
And from now until April 29th,
止まらねえ映像でめちゃまくれっててください！
we'll keep dropping non-stop info, so please look forward to it!
はい！
Right!
ということで改めて、秘密結社ホロックスファーストライブ、
So to recap, Secret Society holoX's 1st Live,
ファーストミッションは、4月29日、PIAアリーナMMにて開催されます！やったー！
"1st Mission," will be held on April 29th, 2026, at Pia Arena MM!
チケット！
Get your tickets!
ゲットして！ゲットして！ゲットして！
Get them! Get them!
はい！
Yes!
もろもろの詳細は後日発表予定とのことですので、
Further details will be announced at a later date,
皆さん、続報を待てでござれ！
so look forward to the updates!
よろしく！よろしく！
See you!
そしてそして、先ほど聞いていただきました新曲、今日ンクスです！聴いていただきましたけれども、この後
And finally, please enjoy a snippet of the new song we just played, "Just for X"!
22時20分よりですね
Starting at 22:20, right?
MVをプレミア公開したいと思います！
we're going to hold the MV premiere!
イェーイ！おおー！いいねー！
Yay! Ohh! Awesome!
かっこいい！おしゃれですね。
So cool! Very stylish.
そしてえ、本日24時ですね、12月2日の0時にデジタルリリースが開始されますので
And, today at 24:00, December 2nd at midnight, the digital release will begin,
ライブに向けてたくさん聞いてくれよな。
so make sure to listen to it a lot for the live!
いや、もうコールできるとこいっぱいあるからね。めためたもう、もうライブのための曲だからね。
Yeah, there are so many places where you can call out! It's made entirely for the live.
まだ新曲いっぱい聞いて、予習して、
Listen to the new songs a lot and study up,
ライブ楽しみにして待っててほしい！
and look forward to the live!
そしてアルバム、シークレットオーダーを持って……持って持って持って持って！
And get the album, Secret Order... get it, get it, get it!
分からないように気をつけてね！もっと、もっとライブ来てね！もっと！
Make sure you don't miss it! Come to the live more! More!
聞いて予習してね！
Listen and study up!
アルバムは、えっと、22時から販売開始ですので！いっぱい買ってね！
The album goes on sale starting at 22:00! Buy lots!
ホロックスをみんな、え、本当に、4周年がありがと……！
Everyone in HoloX, um, thank you so much for the 4th anniversary...!
おめでとう！ありがとう！ありがとう！
Congratulations! Thank you! Thank you!
来年はもうホロックスの我々の年にしていくので、がんばろうね！
Next year will be our year as HoloX, so let's do our best!
5年目もよろしくお願いしますね！
Please look forward to our 5th year too!
おめでとう！ありがとう！
Congratulations! Thank you!
じゃあみんな、せーのでいくよ！せーの！
Well everyone, on three! Ready, go!
バイバーイ！
Bye-bye!
ありがとー！バイバーイ！楽しかった！またねー！
Thank you! Bye-bye! It was fun! See you!